Irini Ibrahim Shoukry Ibrahim

Software Developer

Email: iriniibrahim3@gmail.com

Mobile: +46790762045

Address: Kungshamra 82, 17070 Solna, Stockholm.

Summary

Experienced web developer with two years of experience in building and developing web applications for pharmaceutical and construction companies. Demonstrated skills in C#, ASP.NET, Visual Basic and SQL server. Seeking a challenging role to build my programming career in Sweden. Eager to broaden my experience by acquiring new skills.

Professional Experience

April 2017 - June 2018:

Senior Software Developer at Red Sea Construction, Building and Development, Cairo, Egypt.

January 2016 - March 2017:

Software Specialist - Application Development (IT department) at Global NAPI Pharmaceuticals, Cairo, Egypt.

November 2015 - December 2015:

CIB Customer Service Agent at Commercial International Bank, Cairo, Egypt.

December 2014 - November 2015:

CitiPhone officer at CitiBank-Egypt.

Skills

Programming Languages:

- C#
- VB.Net

Web Developing:

- ASP.Net ASP.NET MVC
- DevExpress
- SharePoint 2013 Developing + CAML Query
- Entity Framework
- JavaScript
- HTML HTML 5 XML
- CSS3/JavaScript /ADO.NET
- JQuery AJAX
- LINQ

Web Designing:

- HTML
- Adobe Photoshop CS5.
- Adobe Dreamweaver CS6.
- Adobe Flash Professional CS5.5.
- Adobe Bridge CS5.
- Adobe Soundbooth CS5.
- Adobe Muse CC Custom

Databases/RDBMS:

- Microsoft SQL Server 2008-2012
- Reporting Services

Basic Concepts:

- Object Oriented Programming
- Database Design

Education

2013 - 2014:

MCIT - 6 Month Scholarship

E-Commerce Track

CompuTek Training Center, Cairo, Egypt.

Graduation Project: Cairo-Portable (Service and Information Web Site).

2009 - 2013:

Bachelor of Computer Science

Higher Institute of Computer and Information Technology,

El Shorouk Academy, Cairo, Egypt. **Graduation Grade:** Good (74.3 %).

Graduation Project: Website Auto Building (Grade: Excellent).

2007 - 2009:

Saint Mary language School, Cairo, Egypt.

Till 2006:

Sahara Language School, Cairo, Egypt.

Certificates

- MCSD: Web Application Solutions Developer.
- MCSD: SharePoint Application Solutions Developer.
- Adobe Muse CC custom.
- YAT Professional Diploma in Web Design 2010.
- SFI level C.

Languages

English: Fluent.Arabic: Native.Swedish: Beginner.

Personal Information

Date of Birth:06/06/1991Nationality:Egyptian.Marital Status:Married.

References are available upon request.